Guide to the El Corno Emplumado Archive 1959-1969 MSS.011
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series C: Printed Materials
  - Subseries 2: Page Proofs
    - Issue #29, pages 1-136. January 1969 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Issue #30, pages 1-184. April 1969 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Issue #30, pages 1-167. April 1969. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous, clippings., undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Subseries 3: Printed Matieral.
    - Issue #24, incomplete. October 1967. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Issue #25, pages 1-38. January 1968. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Issue #27. page 1-37. July 1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Issue #28, pages 1-35. October 1968. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Issue #29. January 1969. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Issue #30, April 1969. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Issue #31, May/June 1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)